# Sue Lee

Full Stack Coding Bootcamp B.S. Education

## **SUMMARY**

Full Stack MERN Web Developer utilizing 8 years of diverse education and leadership background to actively contribute organization and efficiency to the field of web development. Well versed in team work, effective communication, ability to work under pressure, and multitasking. Known by teammates for having a good eye, being solution-oriented, flexible, a good listener, attentive to details and task-oriented.

## **EDUCATION**

## **University of Texas**, Austin — *B.S. Education*

AUGUST 2007 - MAY 2011

Applied Learning and Development EC-6, minor in ESL (GPA 3.7) Study Abroad Fall 2009, Prague, Czech Republic

## **PROJECTS**

## **Sheltr**, Co-Author

React, MongoDB, GraphQL, Express.js, Node.js

MERN stack application that connects users to an animal shelter and saves animals of their liking to make the adoption process easier.

Github: <a href="https://github.com/echo1826/sheltr">https://github.com/echo1826/sheltr</a>
Deployed: <a href="https://sheltr-app.herokuapp.com/">https://sheltr-app.herokuapp.com/</a>

# Feed Your Lifestyle, Co-Author

Handlebars, Express.js, Node.js, Sequelize

Full stack node application that allows users to find recipes based on the diet lifestyle they want to live.

GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/Delmanat3/Feed-Your-Lifesyle">https://github.com/Delmanat3/Feed-Your-Lifesyle</a>
Deployed: <a href="https://feed-your-lifestyle.herokuapp.com/">https://feed-your-lifestyle.herokuapp.com/</a>

## FanJam, Co-Author

MongoDB, Node.js, Express.js, HTML

Full stack node application that creates and tracks a user's daily workout. Logs multiple exercises within cardio or resistance category.

GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/BradMW/FanJam-Project-1">https://github.com/BradMW/FanJam-Project-1</a>
Deployed: <a href="https://bradmw.github.io/FanJam-Project-1/">https://bradmw.github.io/FanJam-Project-1/</a>

Carrollton, TX 75010 Phone: (214) 934-4599

Email: sue.lee0308@gmail.com
GitHub: github.com/suelee0308
LinkedIn:https://www.linkedin.co
m/in/sue-lee-b1b3aa21b/

Portfolio:

sl-portfolio-react.vercel.app

## **CERTIFICATES / LICENSES**

## **Full Stack Web Development**

**Certificate** — University of Texas at

Austin

DECEMBER 2021

## **Real Estate Sales Associate**

**License** — Texas Real Estate

Commission
FEBRUARY 2016

#### EC-6 ESL Generalist License —

Texas Education Agency
MAY 2011

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

MERN Stack - MongoDB, Express.js, React, Node.js

**JavaScript** 

jQuery

mySQL

Sequelize

Mongoose

**RESTful APIs** 

Jest

HTML5

CSS

**Bootstrap** 

Material UI

**Progressive Web Applications** 

Agile Methodology

Kanban

GitHub

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **K12**, Texas — Teacher

FEBRUARY 2021 - AUGUST 2021

- Virtually taught 18 kindergartners who were not offered a virtual option through their local school district during Covid-19, after a condensed onboarding process that required quick learning.
- Flexibility and effective communication needed daily to advise students and parents who were frustrated with virtual learning and technical difficulties.
- Collaborated and analyzed weekly data with 12 teammates to better target students' needs.
- Utilized Newrow Smart Virtual Classroom as platform for online classes.
- Advocated at a state government level for the continuation of virtual learning for the 90% of students who registered for the fall semester.

# Wesley Prep, Dallas, TX — Teacher

AUGUST 2018 - JULY 2020

• Implemented social-emotional teaching techniques for emergent speakers, referring two students to speech-therapy.

# **Plano Independent School District, Plano, TX** — *Teacher*

AUGUST 2012 - JULY 2017

- Effectively oversaw a team of 5 first grade teachers to implement best-practices, refer to student data, and produce a minimum of 90% on-target rate in each class.
- Delegated team duties and relayed information from weekly administrative meetings quickly.
- Consistently communicated with administration and parents to advocate for students' 100% promotion rate.
- Always remained flexible to the needs of students class sizes ranged from 20-25 students.